CHRISTIAN KAMARGA

Houston, TX | christiankamarga@yahoo.com | (713) 417–5748 | linkedin.com/in/christian-kamarga/

SUMMARY

Self-driven Information Systems Master's graduate with 6+ years of experience in providing solutions for data analytical projects. Generated key insights for Google Store advertising campaigns through interpreting big data trends and data processing and visualization KPI reports, directed marketing aspects for delivery project with deadline-focused mindset and adherence to client expectations, model development/validation and presentation, proficient in Python, Tableau, SAS, and SQL, excellent written and verbal communication skills across organizational levels. Open to relocate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Al Prompt Engineer Intern

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

SecureTrust Cyber, Houston, TX

- Collaborated tasks in weekly Scrum team meetings and innovated work processes of securely testing dashboard code by recommending best programming practices in compliance with regulations and security policies.
- Leveraged Streamlit API calls for monitoring and detecting potential risks and threats to organization's end devices.
- Assisted integration of new personnel in remotely setting up client-side Anaconda environments as needed.

Graduate Teaching Assistant

Jan 2022 - May 2022

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

- Coordinated responsibilities for 2 database classes and improved performance towards fulfilling security procedures.
- Created detailed instructions for database installation with troubleshooting steps and mitigated overhead and delays.
- Advised 60+ students weekly in compliance with security protocols and policies with experience in Oracle and SQL.

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information Systems

Dec 2022

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

Perfect Cumulative GPA 4.0

Relevant Graduate Coursework completed:

- Data Communication & Network Security
- Database Management
- Project Management
- Web & Social Analytics

- Data Warehousing & Business Intelligence
- Management of Information Technology
- System Analysis & Design

Bachelor of Science in University Studies

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

Dec 2020

DATA ANALYTICAL PROJECTS

GitHub Project Portfolio: chrismakeskode.github.io/projects/

Group Project Management (At Your Doorstep)

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

Developed and supervised team for implementing a delivery mobile service app. Outlined expectations for risk management and mitigation. Conveyed results in presentation and report and acquired client approval and sign-off.

Google Store E-Commerce Analysis

Jun 2022 – Jul 2022

Analyzed international web traffic patterns of Google Store. Uncovered notable traction among select continents with machine learning models. Provided data-driven suggestions for optimizing prospective marketing campaigns.

Databasing Furniture Store Operations

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Directed and delivered relational database in SQL of a furniture store capable of accurate retention of transactions, inventory, and personnel. Developed to adapt with business and improve client insights.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

May 2024

Cisco

Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer

Aug 2021

Oracle

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software Experience: Java, Python, SQL, Tableau, SAS, Microsoft Office, Hadoop, Oracle, Cisco Packet Tracer, Linux **Creative Applications:** Adobe Creative Cloud, Clip Studio Paint, Photoshop, Autodesk 3DS Max, JavaFX